repair-home.com 2019-01-07

# Privacy Policy | Repair Home

**QuinStreet Privacy Policy**

**LAST UPDATED** : May 25, 2018

QuinStreet, Inc. owns and operates any website that displays this Privacy Policy (each, a “Site”). Your privacy is important to us. We created this Privacy Policy to explain how we collect, use, and share the information that we collect from and about you on this Site. By using this Site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

Information Collected  
Information Use  
Information Sharing  
Other Websites  
Security  
Children  
Choices and Access  
Retention Period  
Operation of Site/Business  
Non-U.S. Residents  
Your California Privacy Rights  
Changes to This Privacy Policy  
QuinStreet Businesses  
Dispute Resolution  
Contact Us

**Information Collected**

_Information You Provide_ : We collect information that you provide to us when you inquire about or purchase products and/or services through this Site. If you refuse to provide any requested information (whether or not required), you may not be able to take full advantage of this Site and its features. That information may include your (a) name, (b) address, (c) e-mail address, (d) telephone number, (e) credit or debit card number, and (f) driver’s license number (for auto insurance offers).

In some cases, we may collect additional information you provide, such as your age, date of birth, gender, occupation, and education level. On our financial services Sites, with your consent, we may collect your Social Security number to verify your identity with a credit bureau and obtain your credit report and credit score. On certain Sites, we may also collect from you information about your contacts, such as their email address, to share an article or other content.

_Information from Third Parties_ : We may also collect information about you from third parties, like credit reporting agencies or a social media site or a plug-in you use to log into or connect to this Site, and authorize to send us information from that social media account (e.g., name, age, photo). We may associate or combine the information you provide through this Site with this information collected from third parties.

_Information Automatically Collected_ : When you use this Site, the server may automatically recognize you by a “cookie” or other tracking technology. These technologies act as unique identifiers and allow us to tailor this Site to your specified interests and keep track of your activity on this Site. This information may be added to your user profile and used to deliver offers and advertisements that we believe are relevant to your interests.

Furthermore, we may retrieve certain information from your browser (e.g., browser type, referrer URL, date and time of your visit, IP address) and device (e.g., MAC address, device type, screen resolution, and OS version). We use this information to monitor this Site’s performance, analyze traffic patterns and usage, ensure that this Site and any transactions function properly, and gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. This information also may be appended to your user profile so that we may further tailor this Site to your interests and send offers to you based on such information.

Our advertisers, publishers and other third-party partners also may utilize third-party cookies and other tracking technologies like clear pixel GIFs (i.e., web beacons) to identify you. We and our third-party partners may use these technologies to measure responses to e-mails and page views on this Site and our third-party partners’ websites. These technologies collect no personal information and are used to enhance this Site, to make this Site more relevant to you, and to measure the effectiveness of our e-mail and advertising campaigns and those of our third-party partners. You can opt out of some of our third-party partners’ use of cookies and other technologies at: <https://www.google.com/settings/ads> (Google), <http://networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp> (various third parties via the Network Advertising Initiative), <http://assets.invitemedia.com/opt-out>.html (Invite Media), and <http://www.clicktale.net/disable.html> (Clicktale).

_Tracking Options and California Do Not Track Disclosures_ : Certain parts of this Site require cookies, and we may use them to deliver more relevant advertising and to link data collected across other devices you use. You can adjust your settings to limit tracking or decline cookies, but as a result you may not be able to use certain features of this Site or take full advantage of all of our offerings. Please refer to your device or browser settings for more information on how to delete or decline cookies and control your tracking preferences. This Site does not respond to do not track signals from most browsers.

**Information Use**

We may use the information we collect from and about you through this Site (a) to connect you with third-party partners who will provide information about products and services; (b) to respond to your inquiries and requests (e.g., newsletters); (c) to market to you and keep you informed of our products and services and/or those of our third-party partners, which we think may be of interest to you; (d) to allow you to send messages to a friend through this Site; (e) to develop new products and enhance and improve our Sites and business; (f) to complete and fulfill any purchase you make; and (g) to use your data in an aggregated, non-specific format for analytic and demographic purposes. Your contact information also may be used to reach you when necessary. With your consent, we may use automated decision-making, including profiling, to analyze the information collected from and about you.

We have a lawful basis for collecting and processing your information if (a) you consented to such processing; (b) we have a legitimate interest for processing your data, like analytics, fraud prevention, improving our Sites and our business, and direct marketing; and (c) we are legally required to process it.

**Information Sharing**

Additionally, we may share your information (a) with other QuinStreet Businesses; (b) with third-party partners who will provide you with information about their product and services; (c) with our third-party service providers who provide services like payment processing, IT, and data analysis; (d) with national credit bureaus to verify your identity and obtain your credit report and credit score; (e) if you seek insurance quotes, with financial services providers who offer competitive rates and/or the Department of Motor Vehicles to verify your driving record, previous claims history, and vehicle VINs; (f) if you choose to send a message through this Site or contribute to public areas of this Site (e.g., message boards, blogs); and (g)with a third party in the event of a sale or transfer of all or part of our business (including in connection with any bankruptcy proceeding).

We also may access and disclose your information to (a) comply with legal process; (b) to respond to lawful requests from authorities, including public and government authorities outside your country of residence, and including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements; (c) to enforce our terms and this Privacy Policy; (d) to protect our business; (e) to protect our rights, privacy, safety, or property and/or that of others; and (f) as necessary under applicable law, including laws outside your country of residence.

**Other Websites**

This Site may contain links to third-party owned and/or operated websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such third-party websites. These third-party websites have separate privacy practices; we have no responsibility or liability relating to such practices; and such practices govern your use of these websites. If this Site includes any mapping features, those mapping features are powered by Google Inc. and governed by Google’s privacy policy: <http://www.google.com/privacy.html>, as amended from time to time.

**Security**

We have taken certain physical, technical, and administrative steps to protect the information we collect from and about Site users. We encrypt sensitive information (such as credit card number and personal health information) provided. Please remember, though, that that neither the transmission of information over the Internet nor the storage of information can ever be 100% secure. If you have reason to believe that your interaction with us is no longer secure please immediately notify us at [info@quinstreet.com](mailto:info@quinstreet.com).

**Children**

We do not knowingly collect, use, or share the personal information of children under age 13 and this Site is not directed to individuals under 13. If we are made aware that we have collected personal information from an individual under age 13 we will delete this information as soon as possible.

**Choices and Access**

Residents of certain countries, including European Union member states (and the United Kingdom), may have additional rights listed under “Non-U.S. Residents” below.

_Marketing E-Mails_ : To stop receiving marketing e-mails from us, please click [here](http://www.emchoice.com/unsubscribe/index.jsp?MERID=3589) and follow the instructions to unsubscribe. Even if you unsubscribe, we may still send administrative (i.e., non-marketing) messages. To unsubscribe from a third party’s communications, contact that third party directly or follow the instructions to unsubscribe in the applicable marketing e-mail.

_Certain Sharing with Third Parties_ : To opt out of our sharing of your personal information with third parties for their own marketing purposes, contact us at [info@quinstreet.com](mailto:info@quinstreet.com) with your name, address, and phone number and request that we suppress your personal information going-forward. The e-mail address you use to send the e-mail must match the e-mail address in our records. Please note that we will not be able to remove your personal information from the third parties’ databases, and you will need to contact them directly and/or use any available opt-out mechanisms.

_Access and Deletion_ : You may ask whether we hold any of your personal information (or request its deletion) by contacting us at [info@quinstreet.com](mailto:info@quinstreet.com) and providing your name, address, and phone number. The e-mail address you use to send the e-mail must match the e-mail address in our records.

**Retention Period**

We will retain your personal information for as long as is needed to provide you with our products and services, unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law. Personal information of non-U.S. residents will be stored for six years unless otherwise required for legal purposes or as set forth in “Non-U.S. Residents” below.

**Operation of Our Site and Business**

Our Site and business are operated in the United States. If you are located outside of the United States any information you provide to us will be transferred to and processed in the United States. By using this Site or providing us with your personal information, you consent to have your personal information transferred to and processed and stored in the United States in the absence of an adequacy decision or the appropriate safeguards set forth in Articles 45 and 46, respectively, of the General Data Protection Regulation.

**Non-U.S. Residents**

For residents of the European Union (and the United Kingdom), QuinStreet, Inc., info@quinstreet.com, is the data controller responsible for your personal information collected under this Privacy Policy. In addition, you have the following rights with respect to the personal information collected from and about you on this Site:

  * The right to request access to such personal information.
  * The right to request the correction, erasure, and/or restriction of processing of such personal information.
  * In some instances, the right to object to the processing of such personal information.
  * In some instances, the right to request that QuinStreet export, in a structured, commonly used, and machine readable format, and transmit to another controller, such personal information.
  * The right to withdraw, at any time, any consent to the processing of such personal information.

To exercise these rights, please contact [info@quinstreet.com](mailto:info@quinstreet.com).

**Your California Privacy Rights**

California law allows Site users that reside in California to ask for information about our practice of sharing your personal information with third parties for their own marketing purposes. We are not obligated to respond to more than one request per calendar year. This Privacy Policy details the types of information we collect and when we share such information, but if you are a resident of California and would like to know the specific companies with whom we shared your personal information and the categories of the information we shared, please send us an email at [info@quinstreet.com](mailto:info@quinstreet.com). Alternatively, you may send a written request to the following address:

**Privacy  
QuinStreet  
950 Tower Lane, 6th Floor  
Foster City, CA 94404**

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do, we will post an updated version of the Privacy Policy and revise the “ **LAST UPDATED** ” date at the top. If we change the Privacy Policy in any material way, we will provide appropriate notice to you. Using this Site after any changes are made means you accept those changes and the revised Privacy Policy.

**QuinStreet Businesses**

For purposes of this Privacy Policy, “you” or “your” means the person(s) using this Site or the products or services offered through this Site. “QuinStreet,” “us,” or “we” includes (but is not limited to) QuinStreet, Inc., QuinStreet Media, Inc., QuinStreet Insurance Agency, Inc., GuideToLenders, QuinStreet Properties, Inc. and QuinStreet PL, Inc. QuinStreet, Inc. is the party responsible for the management of the jointly used information.

**Dispute Resolution**

You have the right to submit feedback about this Privacy Policy, or the practices described in it, to the applicable supervisory authority in your jurisdiction of residence. For U.S. residents this is/includes the Federal Trade Commission and/or your state Attorney General. For Non-U.S. residents this is/includes the Data Protection Authority in your country of residence.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy please contact us at [info@quinstreet.com](mailto:info@quinstreet.com) or:

**Privacy  
QuinStreet, Inc.  
950 Tower Lane, 6th Floor  
Foster City, CA 94404**
